[{"question": " you said you&#146;d marry joey?", "answer": " okay you have to realize, i was exhausted, i was emotional, i would have said yes to anybody. like that time you and i got married!  i&#146;m not helping.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " so you said yes to him, and you just had our baby?", "answer": " that is right and traditionally the daddy is supposed to give the mummy a present but i am prepared to let that go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " so when i came in here to see if you wanted to maybe start things up again, you were engaged to my best friend.", "answer": " well&#151;really? i thought chandler was your best friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " ooooo!", "answer": "  hey you guys i&#146;m gonna take off. i just wanted to let you guys know, say goodbye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " rachel said she&#146;d marry you?!", "answer": "  this isn&#146;t the right room, sorry folks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " ok, i don&#146;t wanna be negative so i&#146;ll say that most of the signs you bought are good.", "answer": " no they ran out of &quot;it&#146;s a girl&quot; but i can fix this one,  see?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  so sexy.  honey.", "answer": " yea yea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " honey why don&#146;t you go lie down.", "answer": " no, no, ross and rachel will be back soon and then i gotta go to the office  am i producing them?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " why&#146;re you so tired?", "answer": " couldn&#146;t sleep last night you know, then i started worrying about this big divisional meeting that i have later today, the more i worried about it the more i couldn&#146;t sleep. y&#146;know? i was like, if i fall asleep now i&#146;ll get six hours sleep, but if i fall asleep now i&#146;ll get five hours sleep. not matter what i did i couldn&#146;t fall asleep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " you know what you should&#146;ve done, you should have told yourself that little story.", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " hi, welcome home!", "answer": " phoebe did the signs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh you guys thanks for doing this.", "answer": " look at all the stuff people sent!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh ah!  oh my gosh there&#146;s something every mother needs, a giant stuffed gorilla that takes up the entire apartment! what are people think&#133;  oh you guys i love it.", "answer": " hey so where&#146;s ross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " he&#146;s downstairs getting the rest of the stuff out of the cab.", "answer": " is he still mad at us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " well, you more then me, but he can&#146;t stay to mad at me. i mean, i just had his baby.", "answer": " that&#146;s not fair! i can&#146;t do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " yeah, i&#146;m not so sure you should be here when he comes up.", "answer": " see this is what i was afraid of, i didn&#146;t think i should be here either but somebody  said he&#146;d be over it by now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " she&#146;s just so cute! i just wanna bite her ear off and use it and a sucking candy.", "answer": " phoebe! but i could take one of those little feet and put it in a pita pocket.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  okay i put most of the stuff away.", "answer": " oh great, the pacifiers?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " in the closet.", "answer": " the burping clogs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " linen closet.", "answer": " the diapers?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " in the hospital.", "answer": " wow you guys got a hospital? fancy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " no i left the diapers at the hospital! there&#146;s some in the bag but i&#146;ll run out and get some more.", "answer": " alright thanks, oh ross could you stop by the coffee house and get me a muffin?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " sure what kind?", "answer": " umm let me think...what do i want, what d-o i w-a-n-t...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " please take your time, it&#146;s an important decision. not like, say, i know! deciding to marry someone, this is about a muffin.", "answer": " blueberry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " blueberry it is.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " wow, he&#146;s really not letting this go, is he?", "answer": " god how long do you think that&#146;s gonna last?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i dunno, well he got over the &quot;we were on a break&quot; thing really quickly.", "answer": " y&#146;know i can&#146;t even worry about that right now, cause i got the cutie little baby, oh i can&#146;t believe how much i love her, i can&#146;t get enough of her, like right now i miss her. i actually miss her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " you know that&#146;s&#133; that&#146;s her.", "answer": " oh god look at her sleeping. oh, i love her so much! oh, i think i&#146;m gonna wake her up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh no, rach, no no, you know you&#146;re never supposed to wake a sleeping baby.", "answer": " well i can do whatever i want! i made her!  come on little girl, hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " i can say i told you so but she&#146;s kinda doing that for me.", "answer": " oh i&#146;m sorry mummy&#146;s so sorry go back to sleep go back to sleep. shh. shhh! go back to sleep", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " breaks your heart doesn&#146;t it", "answer": " it really does&#133; how long do you think we have to stay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " ok if everyone&#146;s on board, it&#146;s settled, chandler,  chandler?", "answer": " yep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " are you on board?", "answer": "  yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " well, alright, we already tried feeding her, changing her, burping her, oh try this one! go back in time and listen to phoebe!", "answer": " alright here&#146;s something, it says to try holding the baby close to your body and then swing her rapidly from side to side.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " it worked!", "answer": " oh  oh no just stopped to throw up a little bit.  oh come on, what am i gonna do, its been hours and it won&#146;t stop crying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " umm, she rach, not it, she.", "answer": " yeah, i&#146;m not so sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh my god, i am losing my mind.", "answer": " yeah, no kidding, this just proves no good can come from having sex with ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " diapers huh?", "answer": " yep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " so i guess rachel had you baby?", "answer": " yep, can you believe it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " nope! i still can&#146;t believe she slept with you in the first place.", "answer": " huh? ooh  you mean like a&#133; huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": "  hey.  ross, i know you&#146;re pissed at me, but we have to talk about this.", "answer": " ah actually we don&#146;t.  joey: fine, fine okay. but i gotta say technically, i didn&#146;t even do anything wrong.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  what!  you didn&#146;t do anything wrong?!", "answer": " i said i didn&#146;t technically.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " okay let&#146;s put aside that you  &quot;accidentally&quot; picked up my grandmothers ring and you  &quot;accidentally&quot; proposed to rachel.", "answer": " look, can i just stop you right there for a second? when people do this  i don&#146;t really know what that means.  you were saying?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " and i can even understand that you couldn&#146;t tell rachel, but why couldn&#146;t you tell me, huh? you had all day to and you didn&#146;t.", "answer": " i know i should&#146;ve.  &quot;i&#146;m sorry.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna go.", "answer": " no, come on ross!  look, ross, we have to get past this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " give me the bag.", "answer": " no, look, i don&#146;t know what else to do. i said i&#146;m sorry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " joey!", "answer": " you should scream at me, or-or-or curse me, or hit me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " i&#146;m not gonna hit you.", "answer": " why not? you&#146;ll feel better! i&#146;ll feel better, and you know you want to. i can see it in your eyes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " no i don&#146;t.", "answer": " a little bit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " little bit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " no!", "answer": "  a little bit more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " give me the bag.", "answer": " no, hit me", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " give me the bag.", "answer": " hit me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " joey, give me the bag.", "answer": " hit me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " joe i&#146;m not kidding&#133;", "answer": "  hit me, hit me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " no!", "answer": "  hit me! hit me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " you ducked!!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry! it was a reflex!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " oh my god, this really hurts!!!", "answer": " i couldn&#146;t help it! when a fist comes at your face, you duck! look!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " what is the matter with you?!?", "answer": " you were supposed to duck!!! why didn&#146;t you duck?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " why don&#146;t we talk about this on the way to the hospital?", "answer": " good, good yeah,  maybe while we&#146;re there, they can check your reflexes.   &quot;oops.&quot; commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " try feeding her again.", "answer": " i already fed her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " i know, that&#146;s why i said again!", "answer": " alright you guys, we can&#146;t turn on each other, okay? that&#146;s just what she wants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " monica can i talk to you outside for a minute?", "answer": " oh no, you guys, just stay here, i&#146;m gonna go check her diaper, pheebs you wanna come?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " oh i&#146;m kinda part of this.", "answer": " actually pheebs its more of a husband and wife kinda thing", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " okay what&#146;s up", "answer": " umm, you know how we always said that it would be fun to move to paris for a year? you know, you could study french cooking and i could write and we could take a picnic along the seine and go wine tasting in bordeaux?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " oh yeah .", "answer": " okay, you know how that people say that tulsa is the paris of oklahoma?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " what? who says that?", "answer": " people who&#146;ve never ever been to paris.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " what&#146;s going on?", "answer": " we&#146;re moving to tulsa!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " excuse me?", "answer": " okay, ms. mckenna, she kind of works above my boss, she asked me to move to tulsa and be the president of our office there, and i was sleeping and apparently, said yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  tulsa, oklahoma!", "answer": " the sooner state, whatever that is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " chandler, i don&#146;t even wanna see the musical oklahoma!", "answer": " really? oh what a beautiful morning! surrey with a fringe on top.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " are you trying to tell me that we&#146;re moving to oklahoma, or that you&#146;re gay? all right, not that this matters, but did they at least offer you a huge raise?", "answer": " no, no, but they are going to lease us a ford focus.  i&#146;ll get out of it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": "  what is wrong with emma?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " umm ma&#146;am, do you have a minute?  i kind of have some bad news. i don&#146;t think i can move to tulsa.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " it&#146;s a funny story, actually.  i kind of fell asleep in the meeting this morning so when i said i&#146;d move to tulsa, i didn&#146;t really know what i was saying.", "answer": " you fell asleep?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " but only because i was up all night worried about this meeting, ain&#146;t that funny? irony? not a fan, alright . see, here&#146;s the thing. i went home and told my wife about tulsa and she won&#146;t go. see, me, i love tulsa! tulsa is heaven! tulsa is italy&#151;please don&#146;t make me go there!", "answer": " chandler, i&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hey, so how is it?", "answer": " i broke my thumb.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " your thumb? that&#146;s weird.  you sure you&#146;re punching right? make a fist.  maybe later. ross i feel terrible.", "answer": " you know what, you can go, i just have to fill out some forms.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " you, you want me to help you with that?", "answer": " why, does it look like i&#146;m having trouble with my misshapen claw?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " name?  i know ross but what&#146;s it short for? you know like, like rossel or rosstepher.", "answer": " just ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " it&#146;s pretty, okay date of birth?", "answer": " you know my birthday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " sure, may...tember.", "answer": " october 18th.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " occupation? dinosaurs.", "answer": " actually i&#146;m a palian&#133; dinosaurs is fine&#133; the drawing is not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " alright, who do you want as your emergency contact?", "answer": " ah, rachel i guess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " okay, relationship, boy this could take a while.", "answer": " just ah&#133; just put roommate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " come on, you guys are more then that! i mean, you&#146;re gonna get together right?", "answer": " i don&#146;t think that we are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " but you two were supposed to be together.", "answer": " well, i thought so too, but then she said she&#146;d marry you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " come on, ross, that didn&#146;t mean anything! she just had the baby, she was all freaked out about doing it alone, she would have said yes to anybody.", "answer": " yeah that&#146;s what she said.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " so?", "answer": " so i don&#146;t wanna be just anybody.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " wow.", "answer": " you know what, it&#146;s, it&#146;s better this way anyway. i mean i don&#146;t know what i was thinking, going down that road again with us. it&#146;s just much easier if we&#146;re just friends who have a kid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " and you&#146;re okay with that?", "answer": " yes. i mean, it&#146;s what we always planned. and if you have a plan, you should stick to it. that&#146;s why they call them plans. hello?  i&#146;m fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " hey, for what it&#146;s worth, with rachel i don&#146;t think you&#146;ll ever be just  &quot;anybody.&quot;", "answer": " hey there you go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " oh my god! how long has she been crying?", "answer": " about a week and a half.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " rach, try holding her a different way.", "answer": " you guys, i&#146;m doing the best i can, anyone else is welcome to try.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " alright, i&#146;ll try, fine! yes, okay!", "answer": " here you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " oh god what am i gonna do you guys, i can&#146;t even comfort my own baby! i&#146;m the worst mother ever!", "answer": " you&#146;re just new at this, it&#146;ll get better, think about your first day at work. i mean, that couldn&#146;t have been easy but you figured that out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " yeah i don&#146;t think dressing provocatively is going to help me here! oh my god just please take her.", "answer": " okay i&#146;ll take her, here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  have i gone deaf?", "answer": " it worked! ooh baby baby baby, ooh baby baby baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " you must be a fireball in bed.", "answer": " i can&#146;t believe it! she&#146;s asleep! i got her to go to sleep! i have actual magical powers!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh my god! you got her to stop crying!", "answer": " yes i did, i&#146;m monica, super aunt", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " you are the official baby crier stopper!", "answer": " yes i am!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " you&#146;re never leaving the apartment!", "answer": " say what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " that&#146;s your new job, day and night, she starts crying i need you here.", "answer": "  oh no no no no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " thankfully you don&#146;t need me at all  so okay super aunt see you later! rachel let&#146;s give it six to eight months .", "answer": " okay so listen i&#146;m gonna go lay down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " you know the book says that whenever she&#146;s sleeping i should be sleeping so&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " shhh! we just got her to go to sleep", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " oh so there can&#146;t be any yelling.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " we&#146;re moving to tulsa", "answer": "  what!?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " heeeeey, where have you been?  what happened to you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " ah i had a little thing with joey, if you think this is bad you should see him.", "answer": " oh no ross! this is not good, we have to talk about this joey thing. please sit.  you have got to get over this joey thing, okay? i never really wanted to marry joey, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " you know what i really really want?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " what, rach?", "answer": " i wanna sleep, i wanna eat, i wanna take a shower, i mean before she wakes up and we gotta do this all over again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": "  right.", "answer": " i mean i got news for you mister, emma? not easy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " well, that&#146;s what i&#146;m here for.  want me to get that?", "answer": " no its really okay&#133; monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " you know, ah, i&#146;ve been thinking about this and i gotta tell ya, it&#146;s not my fault. it&#146;s a natural instinct.", "answer": "  hey, what you guys talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}]